Hearing this friends Vivek, I welcome you all to the
YouTube channel of policybazaar.com friends today we
bring good topics for you today also
our topic can be very
important for all of you okay if you have
taken your policy and you want to cancel it then can
we cancel it
and in how many days can we cancel
it what is it called what is its process
so how to cancel the policy
already voted so I am going to tell you all this in this video
so please
stay with us if you like this video then
please like, share and
also subscribe to our channel so
friends come and watch this video till the end
so what happens is that we
take a policy by keeping a belief someone is
our friend someone is a confidante someone is
in the online policy
sometimes we take the policy ourselves
but later we come to know that some of our
friends this polythene is very bad someone
becomes our second insurance he
understood when it is better for hair then this is it
or sometimes  What happens is that
after taking the policy we come to know that a
problem has come up, I need money,
so I want to cancel that too for polyp cancer, if for
any reason I want to cancel the policy then how can I
select, okay, so in that there is a
free look period for it,
IRDA which is the Insurance
Regulatory and Development Authority, they have
given a time to each type of policy,
it is called free look period, you have been
given a time within that time you
can cancel the policy, if you have
taken an airplane policy, someone
filled this form at your home, physically filled the form, collected the cheque, deposited it
at your home by post, it is
in your hand, after the day the policy came in your hand,
if it is an addition
quote, then TDS and if it is life insurance then
you have 30 days time, okay, you
can cancel the policy within 30 days, if the life insurance is more or less
then 15 days or there were
different terms and conditions of different policies,
then at least you are going to get 15 days,
excluding motor  I request you to
leave the car and go
to the branch from the college and here the policy and its receipt,
your ID proof of address proof, an
application and if their format is there then
why did they refuse the application and its revision properties on that format, I am
not satisfied with this policy, I was
not explained properly or a policy came in
which one thing is written and what I have heard is that I am
not happy with these conditions, you can
also say this, you can select the policy
and
I have done my duty now, you will not get the fool, you will get all the
rest of the money, if your
health checkup has been done, ok, even then the
company can cancel the cheque money, it is as per the
rules and regulations of their respective companies,
but largely your money will be returned,
ok, so see, first of all, we take the service positive
term insurance policy on trust
and sometimes we are not told what all you get in it,
what are the coughs in it and in this, some other
company is also offering a good plan in competition,
I cannot tell, hence I would
request you to fill your form yourself,
what would be the policy normally  It is that if
any judgment of yours comes then the policy will definitely be
EMI, then he will definitely get the cover, the
destination is anyone's MS Word and body mass
index height is 5.5 and weight is
110 kg, then Vijay Mishra is matching,
he is going to get the policy
office or someone is on insulin
but this leave is less then without
medical checkup he can get interest, if
he hid it then what all was
noted in the form in the place,
proposal form submission was taken in front of you, polish or ghee and
15H field flat was allowed to end, that's it,
you had to take the policy, you will
not be able to get it by asking, in this if you
take the policy online then you have to
fill the form yourself, the companies call you,
how have you filled it, there is
telephonic verification also and if you
beat yourself then you will not hide anything
because why would I say anything wrong in my form, so you
want it online, you want it on our website
policybazaar.com, enemies
photo Mishra shop and compare it so that it does
not happen that later you see something of mine
on the corporation, you have to fill at least five or till the companies  You will
get a good bag from the company,
where you will be able to recover the images,
see, and I want to tell you one thing, if the
quality is not available online then its cover
images will be to you, as soon as you
get the email, from there your free
mode will be activated, the hard copy of the policy in offline
and you will
receive the policy online,
after that the look at bed time will start,
now you can deposit it in Neeraj, if
you want to cancel this, the
policy holder of yours or his right is iodine on the face,
so we tried to tell you
how we can cancel the policy, those who are
worried because someone
sold me the policy, then do not panic,
your friends, if you have taken the policy for a voice
or someone of your relatives has
sold it to you and the policy which is not going to be available to you for years, then
you
can go and cancel it without telling him, cancel the policy, the policy
money
can come back to you, so friends, if you like the video then
definitely like and share it, it is
important for all of your friends to benefit, so please
comment  You can also put in it what other
topics you want videos on,
so thanks for watching the video
friends, thanks for giving your time, thanks a lot,
stay with us, thank you bye